proxibid.com 2016-03-28

# Proxibid Privacy Policy

At Proxibid, your privacy is one of our highest priorities. We provide this Privacy Policy to help you make an informed choice about your personal information. We desire to be open and honest at all times about information collected from you, how that information is used, and your rights regarding that information.

## NOTICE

 **POLICY ACCEPTANCE**

  * This privacy policy applies to all information collected by or supplied to [www.proxibid.com](http://www.proxibid.com/). By visiting [www.proxibid.com](http://www.proxibid.com/) you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy
  * If you choose to visit [www.proxibid.com](https://www.proxibid.com/), your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Unified User Agreement, including limitations on damages and application of the law of the State of Nebraska. 

**POLICY AMENDMENTS AND AMENDMENT NOTIFICATION**

  * Please note that we review our privacy practices periodically and such policies are subject to change. Proxibid reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting revisions on the Proxibid Web site. Use of information we gather now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of use. We ask that you periodically review this page to ensure familiarity with the most current version of our Privacy Policy. 
  * In the event of any material amendment to the Privacy Policy, you may be required to affirmatively accept the amended Privacy Policy in order to continue to use the Web site. This Privacy Policy is not intended to, and does not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party. 

**POLICY QUESTIONS**

  * If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@proxibid.com](mailto:privacy@proxibid.com)

 **DISPUTE RESOLUTION**

  * If you believe your complaint has not been adequately addressed by Proxibid, you can raise any concerns with [PrivacyTrust](http://www.privacytrust.org/complaint/raise_privacy_complaint.php), and they will serve as a third party contact to facilitate resolution of any dispute.

 **SAFE HARBOR PARTICIPATION**

  * In accordance with our commitment to protect personal privacy, Proxibid complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Proxibid has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. These principles and FAQs may be found at: <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor>

## COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

 **OVERVIEW**

  * Proxibid collects information from each user of the Proxibid Web site that creates a bidder account with Proxibid (a "Buyer").
  * Proxibid also collects information from each auction company that creates a seller account with Proxibid ("Seller").
  * Proxibid's purpose is to provide Buyers an opportunity to participate in live auctions when they cannot be physically present at the auction site. Proxibid broadcasts the live auction over the Internet and allows Buyers to place bids in real time. Proxibid can also place automated bids on behalf of a Buyer unable to personally monitor the auction broadcast. Proxibid also provides timed online auctions services. 
  * All auctions are operated by independent Sellers. Proxibid has no control over operation of the actual auctions. Proxibid only maintains the Internet interface between the Seller and Buyer. Each Buyer expressly authorizes Proxibid to deliver the Buyer information to any Seller conducting an auction in which the Buyer participates. See "Disclosure of Buyer Information to Sellers" below. Sellers may or may not have their own privacy policies. 

**INFORMATION COLLECTED BY PROXIBID**

  * Proxibid collects contact information to sign you up as a Buyer or Seller. Buyer information is provided to the individual Sellers when a Buyer applies for participation in one of their auctions. 

  * Proxibid requires each **Buyer** who creates an account on Proxibid.com to voluntarily submit the following "Primary Data", regardless of whether the Buyer participates in any auction: 
    * First Name
    * Last Name
    * E-mail Address
    * Date of Birth
    * Country
    * Preferred Language

  * Proxibid requires each **Buyer** to create the following for security purposes: 
    * Username
    * Password
    * Security Question

  * When a **Buyer** participates in an auction, Buyer may be asked to submit the following "Secondary Data" before the Buyer is allowed to place a bid: 
    * Phone Number
    * Type of Phone Line
    * Billing Information including Credit Card and CVV2
    * Shipping Address
    * State Tax Identification Number (if requested by the Seller)
    * Social Security Number to verify Buyer's identity using AuctionGuard? to determine Buyer's eligibility to participate in certain auctions. Proxibid stores only the last four digits of any Social Security number. 

  * Proxibid requires each **Seller** who creates an account on Proxibid.com to voluntarily submit the following information: 
    * Auction Company Name
    * Contact Name
    * Address - including City, State, Country, Zip
    * Phone Number
    * Fax Number
    * E-mail Address
    * Website URL

  * Proxibid requires each **Seller** to create the following for security purposes: 
    * Username
    * Password
    * Security Question

  * In addition, Proxibid requires each **Seller** to submit a merchant application with the following information: 
    * For primary contact person and individuals with access to account: Name, Title, Phone, E-mail, Date of Birth, Last four digits of Social Security number, Residential address 
    * Primary Category of Items Selling
    * Auctioneer License Number and Name on License
    * Auction Association Affiliations
    * Tax Id Number
    * Date Business Commenced
    * Type of Business (sole proprietorship, partnership, corporation, non-profit, other)
    * Company URL
    * Estimated Number of Monthly Transactions Online
    * Average Transaction Amount
    * Bankruptcy History
    * Copy of Formation Document (Certificate of Incorporation, etc.)

  * In addition to information provided directly to Proxibid in connection with Buyer profiles and participating in auctions, Proxibid automatically collect and analyze the following information for internal purposes only to allow our software to function properly and to validate your bids: 
    * Computer Networking Interfaces (includes Internal IP Address) (also used for risk/fraud prevention purposes)
    * External IP Address
    * Host Name
    * Username Defined by the Operating System (usually not any real person's name)
    * Java Runtime; Java Vendor; Java Version
    * JVM Name; JVM Version
    * Operating System
    * Operating System Architecture - 32-bit or 64-bit
    * Operating System Version; Patch Level
    * User Home Directory
    * Browser Type; Browser Version
    * Operating System Time Zone; Language; Country
    * Details of Available CPUs
    * Number of Processor Core
    * Name of Personal Computer
    * Screen Height (in pixels); Screen Width (in pixels).

## ACCESS TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

  * Buyers and Sellers may obtain access to their personal information to review, update and correct using the Proxibid web site.
  * Buyers and Sellers may withdraw personal information by contacting Proxibid at 1-877-505-7770.
  * Requests to withdraw personal information could render the Buyer?s or Seller?s account inactive.

## COMMUNICATION OPT-IN / REMOVAL

  * Our Web site gives you the opportunity to opt-in to receive communication from Proxibid and our partners at the point where you create your account. If you wish to remove your information from our database to stop receiving communications or our service, you may send an E-mail to:marketing@proxibid.com. 
  * Please note that Buyers who opt out may still receive communications from Sellers. Opting out of Proxibid communications has no impact upon a Seller's use of Buyer information. Buyers should contact a Seller directly to opt out of communications from a Seller. 
  * SMS Text Disclosure. Opt in via [www.proxibid.com](http://www.proxibid.com/) to receive SMS Text message containing auction reminders, offers acceptances and other notifications. By opting-in you specifically acknowledge that your wireless carrier may charge for messages sent or received and that you are solely responsible for such charges and that Proxibid may collect, use and disclose the information you provide to enable this service. Message frequency is variable and based on your subscription to receive notifications. One message per request for auction reminders. Text STOP to 25884 to opt out. For support: Text HELP to 258841, call 1-877-505-7770 or email [info@proxibid.com](mailto:info@proxibid.com). Participating carriers include: Alltel, AT&T, MetroPCS, Cricket, T-Mobile, U.S. Cellular, Sprint, Google Voice, Cincinnati Bell, Virgin Mobile and Verizon Wireless. 

## USE OF INFORMATION

  * EXCEPT AS DISCLOSED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY, WE DO NOT SELL, TRADE, RENT OR OTHERWISE DISCLOSE ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION TO ANY THIRD-PARTIES, UNLESS YOU EXPRESSLY GIVE US PERMISSION TO DO SO. HOWEVER, YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE SHARED WITH AFFILIATES, AGENTS, OR CONTRACTORS OF PROXIBID, AS NECESSARY, TO PROVIDE SERVICES TO YOU. 

  * **Your personal information is used in the following ways:**
    * User IDs and Passwords - Provides you with access to your profile and to protected content;
    * Account Information - Provides us with information about who you are and how to contact you, along with any preferences you have provided, such as language, E-mail format and interests. Also, provides us with data for internal auditing and reporting; 
    * AuctionGuard? - Provides us with information needed to determine eligibility in specific auctions. AuctionGuard? is Proxibid's proprietary software that relies on FastData? and Financial Transmission Network, Inc., as well as a Buyer's history within Proxibid's platform, to determine a Buyer's eligibility "score." Sellers may use this score to allow or to limit eligibility for certain auctions. Accordingly, a Buyer's AuctionGuard? score may be disclosed to a Seller in connection with a Buyer's application to participate in the Seller's auction; 
    * Customer Feedback and Support - Provides you with a mechanism for requesting information from Proxibid. Also, provides you with a mechanism to tell us how we can improve our services and site design; 
    * E-mail Correspondence - Provides us with an avenue to raise and respond to issues and inquiries of all types. Also, provides us a way to distribute information about Proxibid services and upcoming auctions. 
  * **Cookies**
    * Our site places a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. "Cookies" are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard disk for record keeping purposes. Our site uses cookies during your online session to deliver content specific to your interests. Cookies allow us to avoid showing you the same ad or message repeatedly and allow us to tailor our site to you. Our cookies enable us to relate your use of our site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided to our site. Most Internet browsers enable you to erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions. 
  * **Public Forums**
    * Proxibid may provide its users with chat rooms, forums, message boards and/or news groups. Please remember that any information disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. Please also note that Proxibid is not responsible for any content posted in these areas. Although Proxibid has the right to monitor all information disclosed in these areas, it is under no obligation to do so. 
  * **Children's Privacy**
    * Proxibid understands the importance of protecting children's privacy in the interactive, on-line world. Proxibid does not intentionally target or solicit to children thirteen (13) or younger for purposes of collecting personal information. The Proxibid Web site may link to certain Web sites which may target or solicit to children thirteen (13) or younger and may collect personal information. Those Web sites are not governed by this Privacy Policy, but will (or should) have their own privacy policies that more fully explain how they respect and protect the privacy of children while providing them information, goods or services. Check out the [Federal Trade Commission's site](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/edu/pubs/consumer/tech/tec08.shtm) for more tips on protecting children's privacy online. 

## DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

We will only disclose your information to a third party when (i) the disclosure is consistent with this Privacy Policy; (ii) you otherwise expressly authorizes the disclosure; or (iii) we are ordered to disclose the information in a judicial or administrative proceeding and have provided written notice to you of such order (see "DISCLOSURE REQUIRED BY LAW" below).

 **DISCLOSURE OF BUYER INFORMATION TO SELLERS**

  * Each Buyer expressly authorizes and directs Proxibid to deliver to the Seller any information Buyer has provided to us which is requested by the Seller in order for Buyer to participate in an auction. This may include any and all information listed above under "Information Collected by Proxibid." Buyer also authorizes us to disclose Buyer's AuctionGuard? "score" to any Seller which requests such information to determine Buyer's eligibility to participate in an auction. 
  * Buyer acknowledges and agrees that Proxibid has no responsibility whatsoever regarding the Seller's use of the information. Once we deliver Buyer's information to a Seller, the information will be governed by the Seller's privacy policy, if any. Proxibid has no control over and no obligation to monitor the Seller's use of Buyer information. Before a Buyer participates in any Seller's auction, Buyer should review that Seller's privacy policy, if any, to understand how Buyer's information will be handled. 

**DISCLOSURE TO THIRD PARTIES**

  * Your information may be disclosed to unaffiliated third-parties in the following situations:
    * To vendors and service providers engaged by Proxibid to perform services or functions on behalf of Proxibid. Such third-parties shall be obligated to use your personally identifiable information solely in connection with providing such services; 
      * To enforce our Unified User Agreement or otherwise protect our rights;
      * To resolve disputes between users;
      * We may disclose bidding and price information, auction item descriptions, and other auction data to third-parties
      * In connection with a proposed or actual sale, merger, transfer, or exchange of all or a portion of Proxibid. As Proxibid continues to mature, it is possible that Proxibid or substantially all of its assets may be acquired. In such a transaction, customer information will be one of the transferred business assets 

**DISCLOSURE AS REQUIRED BY LAW**

  * Unfortunately, due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose information to the government under certain circumstances, or may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. Further, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will remain private. 

## EXTERNAL LINKS

  * Our site may contain links to other internet Web sites. We encourage all of our partners, contributors and third-parties to implement policies and practices that respect the privacy of our users. However, Proxibid is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. Our policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties, whether they are linked from the Proxibid Web site, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the personal information disclosed to them. Because Proxibid does not control the privacy policies of third-parties, you are subject to the privacy policies of that third party. We strongly suggest that you visit the privacy policy of those Web sites to learn about the collection and use of your personal information. 

## RETENTION AND DISPOSAL OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

  * Personal information is not disposed of as we keep all information regarding the selling and purchase of each lot, but all applicable information is managed to ensure the privacy expectations set forth in this policy.

## SECURITY

  * Proxibid has security measures in place to help protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of the information under our control. We restrict access to your personal identification and contact information within the company to only those authorized employees who need to use that information for a specific job function. 

  * Though Proxibid employs security measures designed to safeguard online transactions and personal information, we cannot be responsible if a third-party gains access to the database or your personal or credit card information by evading our security measures. If you become aware of any breach of data security or have any other questions regarding the security of our site, please contact us at [privacy@proxibid.com](mailto:privacy@proxibid.com). 

## POLICY LAST AMENDED:

  * August 13,2015 

? 2015 Proxibid, Inc. All rights reserved. Proxibid, the Proxibid logo, and AuctionGuard are trademarks of Proxibid, Inc. FastData is a registered trademark of First Data Integrated Services Inc. All other brands, product names or trademarks referenced are the property of their respective owners.
